

CONTACT ME

♀ 1507, sec-7, Karnal, Haryana

rajat.karnal@gmail.com

L +91 9034101507

Rajat-Raghuvanshi-1507

EDUCATION

B.E CSBS

Chandigarh University

CGPA (current) - 8.7

2020 - 2024

Senior Secondary (XII), Science

Pratap Public School, Karnal

Percentage - 92.6% 2019 - 2020

SKILLS

Javascript

React

MERN stack

React Native

Solidity

LANGUAGE

HINDI ENGLISH

Rajat Raghuvanshi

Full Stack Web Developer

Portfolio - https://rajat-raghuvanshi.netlify.app

ABOUT ME

Creative web developer with experience in building, optimizing and maintaining the performance of user centric websites. Clear understanding of modern technologies and best design practices. An ambitious problem solver willing to join a team of like-minded people.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer (Team Head)

November 2022 - May 2023

Duckcart (currently working)

Lead the team of 12 members, optimized and maintained main server(AWS) of the company along with the database(MongoDb). Added numerous features like Payment Gateways, Notifications, International currency conversion. Played an important role in the development of new Startup website. Learnt important tools like **Slack, Jira, Notion** etc.

Full Stack Web Developer (Intern)

February 2022 - June 2022

QWings

Polished my MERN stack skills and worked along with seniors in maintaining the main website of the company. Updated my old coding skills and learnt time management. Added features related to backend like login, signup, authentication and saving data to database. Also learned advanced and cutom hooks used in react to **optimize** the website and provide **best user experience**.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Krypt (React + Solidity)

September 2022 - October 2022

Link: https://krypt-georli.netlify.app

June 2022 - July 2022

Link: https://chat-app-c8964.web.app

Chat App (React + Firebase)

Shop Buddy (MERN Stack)

January 2022 - March 2022

Link: https://shop-buddy.onrender.com

Voyage (MERN Stack)

September 2021 - October 2021

Link: https://voyage-tours.netlify.app

HOBBIES









Football

Music

ıvel

Gym